Nguyen Thi Chi Lam

SOFTWARE DEPLOYMENT STAFF



Date of birth 15/10/2001

Gender Female

Address
District 5, Ho Chi Minh City

Phone 0967423249

Email nguyenlam151001@gmail.com

Website linkedin.com/in/lâm-nguyễn-a42b31286

Objective

Leverage passion for mobile games and analytical skills to support market research, collect and evaluate data on competitors. Desire to develop experience in game research, analyze player experience and contribute to product development strategy, thereby helping to improve game quality and meet market demand.

Skills

- Project Management: Jira/Confluence, Trello
- Data Organization & Management: Excel, Google Sheets
- Data Analysis & Processing: PowerBI, Excel
- Accounting Information Systems (AIS)
- Soft Skills: Analytical Thinking, Problem-Solving, Communication and Collaboration

Activities

June 2020 - Sep 2020

Manga Trans & Edit Team

Volunteer Translator

May 2020 - Jun 2020

UIT SAFE Volunteer

Participate in the volunteer movement to measure the temperature of students, lecturers and visitors to UIT during the Covid19 outbreak.

Dec 2019

UIT ENGLISH SPEAKING CONTEST

Participate in the English contest about the era of technological development.

Certifications

Experience

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

CJ OLIVENETWORKS VINA

Business Analyst & QA Tester Intern

Business Analyst:

- Analyzed As-is business processes and proposed To-be process improvements.
- Designed contract management screen mockups, ensuring an user-friendly interface.
- Defined business requirements and documented workflows using Jira/Confluence for project tracking.

OA Tester:

- Developed detailed test cases and conducted functional testing before deployment.
- Performed scenario-based testing to ensure system reliability.
- Reported and tracked software defects using Jira, collaborating closely with developers to improve product quality.

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

Freelance Pet Broker (Cat Trading Consultant)

- Acted as an intermediary between cat owners and buyers, negotiating fair deals.
- Researched market trends to match potential buyers with suitable cat breeds.
- Advised customers on pet selection and basic care.
- Closed multiple transactions and earned commissionbased revenue.

Education

Oct 2019 - Nov 2024

UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY - UIT

Major: Information System